MICHAEL LINDBERG

UI/UX DESIGNER/DEVELOPER
MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER

RELEVANT SKILLS

UX/UI DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

- WIREFRAMING
- MOCKUPS
- PROTOTYPING
- USER FLOWS
- PERSONAS
- UX RESEARCH METHODS
- USER TESTING
- ACCESSIBILITY
- AGILE WORKFLOW
- USER CENTERED DESIGN
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript/jQuery

SOFTWARE:

- ADOBE XD
- PHOTOSHOP
- ILLUSTRATOR
- INDESIGN
- AFTER EFFECTS
- PREMIERE PRO
- LUCIDCHART
- UXPRESSIA (JOURNEY MAPPING)
- QUALTRICS

GENERAL SKILLS

BILINGUAL ENGLISH/SPANISH
PROFESSIONAL COMMUNICATION
PROJECT MANAGEMENT
CUSTOMER SERVICE
TEAM PLAYER



PROFILE

I bring professional work experience and people skills together to accomplish tasks and solve problems. My approach is positive and hard working, regardless of the task or time available. I'm always striving to learn more and never stop progressing.

Online Portfolio: mlsk8r.github.io



WORK HISTORY

UX/UI DESIGNER

BRIGHAM YOUNG UNIVERSITY

06/2020 - PRESENT: Research, analyze, design, test, and implement new user experience features and enhancements for applications and websites to meet the needs of campus partners and their varying user audiences. Apply other skills for varying web and graphic design needs.

WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER SOUTHERN UTAH UNIVERSITY

08/2017 - 06/2020: Design, develop, and maintain the user experience and user interface of university websites for campus partners/stakeholders. Develop features to enhance user experience. Use the latest web standards and practices to enhance user experience and accessibility.

WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA

08/2016 - 08/2017: Design and develop websites for campus partners/stakeholders. Develop within the Drupal CMS as well as creating non-CMS static websites using the latest web standards and practices.

MULTIMEDIA SPECIALIST DIXIE STATE UNIVERSITY

08/2014 - 09/2016: Design, develop, and maintain the university websites. Additionally, create digital and print media in various forms for campus departments.

IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN DIXIE STATE UNIVERSITY

03/2013 - 08/2014: Provide IT support to more than 500 campus staff and faculty members. Manage IT projects from start to finish. Provide excellent customer support.



EDUCATION

M.S. GRAPHIC INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY

2017 - 2019 4.0 GPA

B.S. COMPUTER INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY DIXIE STATE UNIVERSITY

2014 - 2016 3.5 GPA

NN/G UX CERTIFIED NIELSEN NORMAN GROUP UX CERTIFICATION

ISSUED FEB 2021

ASSOCIATE OF ANIMATION AND VFX DAVE (Digital Animation & Visual Effects) SCHOOL

2009 - 2010 GRADUATED TOP 3 IN A CLASS OF 28

CONTACT



MCHL.LNDBRG@GMAIL.COM



801.400.7780

ONLINE PORTFOLIO



MLSK8R.GITHUB.IO



LINKEDIN.COM/IN/MLINDBERG1